Guide to the Robert F. Curl Academic papers, 1953- 2012, bulk 1985-1993 MS 483
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series XII: Correspondence, 2005-2008
  - Certificates
    - Ink Drawing of Curl (Box 32, Item 12)
    - Ponca City, Oklahoma: Robert F. Curl Day, 1997 (Box 32, Item 13)
    - Argentina: Distinguished Visitor, Buenos Aires, 1996 (Box 32, Item 14)
    - Time Magazine, 1996-10-21 (Box 32, Item 15)
    - Mexico: Institute of Science and Technology, 2011 (Box 32, Item 16)
    - France: University du Littoral Cote D'Opale: Honorary Doctorate, 2002 (Box 32, Item 17)
    - Council on Competitiveness: Award for Public Service, 2012 (Box 32, Item 18)
    - Mexico: Instituto Politecnico Nacional, 2011 (Box 32, Item 19)
    - Rice University Distinguished Alumni Award, 1997 (Box 32, Item 20)